realtybiznews.com 2012-12-30

# Privacy - RealtyBizNews.com -Real Estate News, mortgage news, real mortgage rates, and commercial real estate

### RealtyBizNews Statement on Privacy

We will always work to maintain your Internet privacy

**Privacy Guidelines**

**One**  
RealtyBizNews will explicitly ask when personal information is needed which may personally identify the user. In General, this information is only requested when the user registers for special features or other site sections that require signup. Personal information may also be requested for entering sweepstakes or contests, and for a variety of other functions, but the user’s permission will be requested before any of his/her information is released.

**Two**  
RealtyBizNews websites and their service partners, will only user your Personal Information to operate their suggested sites, and to better serve their users. It is not our intent to broadcast, sell, or otherwise use any user information. RealtyBizNews is about communicating information to readers and users, and not communicating personal information for business or other purposes. This is our clear message.

**Three**  
If for any reason in the future any RealtyBizNews offering desires to use or release your personal information, we will ALWAYS request your permission. Furthermore, once your permission is granted, RealtyBizNews will provide a simple method for users to withdraw or discontinue said permission. The user will always have the right and ability to discontinue any service or permission at any time.

**Four**  
RealtyBizNews may disclose Personal Information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to abide by suggested laws, protect or defend our rights and property, or ensure the personal safety of our users.

**Five**  
If the user believes at any time that his/her rights to privacy are infringed upon, the owners and staff of RealtyBizNews will treat such concerns with the utmost attention. We are, after all, Web innovators who helped create the current privacy structure of the world wide web. Please contact us via email at privacy@realtybiznews.com, or via phone at **901 290 7037** any time you feel your privacy may be at stake.

> _**But the time has come for journalists to acknowledge that a zone of privacy does exist —-**_ **Roger Mudd**
